Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
Office of Physical Planning Records
1869-1994
1946-1994
University Archives
Princeton University. Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections
Princeton University. Office of Physical Planning.
AC154
107 boxes
3 folders
160 items
The Office of Physical Planning was the division of Princeton University's Department of Facilities charged with oversight of the construction of new buildings on campus and alterations to existing structures. The records consist of office files and architectural drawings in a variety of formats.
Scope and Contents
The Office of Physical Planning Records document the activities of Physical Planning, one division of Princeton University's Department of Facilities, and are primarily related to the construction and modification of buildings and other structures on Princeton's campus. The records contain a variety of documents, including correspondence between Physical Planning and contractors/designers, interoffice memoranda describing potential projects, invoices for work completed, and studies and reports pertaining to the campus. Additionally, as the Office of Physical Planning was at one point the central repository for all architectural drawings and maps of campus, this type of material (in oversized and microform formats) constitutes a significant portion of the records.
Please see series descriptions in contents list for additional information about individual series.
Conditions Governing Access
All architectural drawings transferred by the Office of Physical Planning to the University Archives are open for research use. Other records are closed for a period of ten years from the date the record's creation.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Series 2: Architectural Drawings (Microform) consists of microform aperture cards.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Office of Physical Planning Records were transferred to the Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library in several accessions. The files which comprise Series 1: Building Project Records were transferred between 1996 and 2002, Series 2: Architectural Drawings (Microform) were transferred in 1986, and the bulk of the documents which comprise Series 3: Architectural Drawings (Oversized) were transferred to the library between 1972 and 1980. An small selection of maps were acquired in 2017 and added to Series 3.
Appraisal
Appraisal has been conducted according to Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library guidelines. Nothing was removed from the records during 2007 processing.
The Fire Files Series, which consisted of a numbered set of oversized architectural drawings, were returned to the Office of Physical Planning in 2016.
Accruals
Though the Office of Physical Planning has deactivated, transfers of similar records from the Office of Design and Construction and other divisions in the Department of Facilities are expected in the future.
Related Materials
The Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library holds many collections which relate to the development of Princeton's grounds and buildings, both from an administrative and a historical perspective. Chief among these are the Department of Facilities Operations and Maintenance Records (AC041), the Department of Grounds and Buildings Technical Correspondence Files (AC035), the Department of Grounds and Buildings Historical Subject Files (AC110), and the Robert Judson Clark Papers (AC208). The Board of Trustees Minutes and Records (AC120) also relate to the topic of campus development, particularly those records generated by the Committee on Grounds and Buildings found in Series 5 Subseries 4.
Additionally, the University Archives holds the Office of Physical Planning's University Chapel Stained Glass Windows Restoration Records (AC231), the Nassau Hall Iconography Collection (AC177), which contains historical depictions of one of Princeton's most recognizable buildings, and the Princeton Artwork Collection, which contains representations of other campus locations.
Finally, the University Land Records (AC028) include maps and surveys of the campus and other land owned by Princeton University, which were not necessarily generated or used by the Office of Physical Planning.
Princeton University. Office of Physical Planning.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Physical Planning was the division of Princeton University's Department of Facilities charged with oversight of the construction of new buildings on campus and alterations to existing structures. The primary responsibility of Physical Planning was the management of construction of major structures and alterations to existing structures on the Princeton campus. Physical Planning also arranged for interior design, furniture planning, and landscape design in and around campus buildings. Its other duties included providing long-range planning support for campus building projects, particularly in regards to land use and zoning considerations as well as the maintenance of campus graphics including building plans and maps.
The antecedent to the Office of Physical Planning can be found in the Grounds and Buildings Committee of the Trustees, established in 1876. At the time of its formation the committee appointed a single individual to act as the Curator of Grounds and Buildings, later known as the Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings. As the campus grew in size so too did the level of staffing required for its management and maintenance. In 1964 the title of the position was changed accordingly to Manager of the Division of Physical Planning, and once again in 1986 to Director of Physical Planning. These changes in title were often spurred by the frequent arrival of new personnel, and the most singularly consistent figure in the administration of the Office of Physical Planning was Jon D. Hlafter *61, who served as its director from 1969-2004.
The title of the larger administrative department of which the Office of Physical Planning was a part also changed frequently throughout the University's history. At various times it was known as Grounds and Buildings; Property and Physical Facilities; Physical Planning and Facilities; and Planning, Plant and Properties. Since 1983, the department has simply been known as the Department of Facilities. Headed by the University Vice-President for Facilities, the Department of Facilities and its subsidiary units are located in the MacMillan Building.
Jon Hlafter's acceptance of the position of University Architect in 2004 came amid a reorganization of the Department of Facilities which resulted in the end of the Office of Physical Planning as it had been known. The tasks that had been overseen by Physical Planning were distributed among several newly created Facilities divisions, with the Office of Design and Construction being most analogous to the old Physical Planning office.
Buildings -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; Buildings -- Repair and Construction -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; Campus planning -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; College buildings -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; College Buildings -- Remodeling.; Princeton university; Princeton University. Dept. of Facilities.
- Series 1: Building Project Records, 1879-2002 July 2; 91 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  All architectural drawings transferred by the Office of Physical Planning to the University Archives are open for research use. Other records are closed for a period of ten years from the date the record's creation.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1: Building Project Records consists of files which pertain to projects undertaken by the Office of Physical Planning, which include both the construction of new buildings as well as modifications to existing structures. The files contain a variety of documents including correspondence, invoices, drawings, surveys, meeting minutes, and in some cases photographs.
  Arrangement
  The arrangement of the records at the time of transfer has been retained. Records relating to the same project are generally grouped together by building name or project location. Since many campus structures have been the subject of Office of Physical Planning projects on more than one occasion, they appear multiple times in the folder listing.
  - Building Forms A-Z, 1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - R. E. Schultz File, 1963-1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Temporary Assignment, 1969-1974; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Forrestal Space - Ed Morse, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Space Inventory - Other University, 1966-1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary Report on Allocation of Certain Academic Space, 1964; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Central Campus Study and Space Allocation, 1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Space Study, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Space Survey, 1970-1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Space Allocation Work Sheets, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Space Survey Notes, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Form 15 Requests - Space, 1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Hall, 1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alternative Energy Center, 1979; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Civilization Program, 1972; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Development 865, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - East Pyne, circa 1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - English 190, 1969-1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - European Cultural Studies, 1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - School of Engineering, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Financial Vice President 825, 1971-1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Food Services, 1969; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Forrestal, 1970-1978; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Frick, 1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 5 Ivy Lane, 1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Linguistics, 1969 -1974; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Military Science, 1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - National Organization for Women - University League Nurseries, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Non-academic, Non-student, 1970-1976; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Office of Research and Project Administration, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Palmer Hall, 1970-1977; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Personnel, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Firestone Library, 1963-1977; 1 box
    - Firestone Library Miscellaneous Forms, 1963-1973; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Firestone Library Addition 6701, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Firestone Library Addition 6701, 1965-1972; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Firestone Library 6701 Completed, 1967-1973; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Firestone Library Social Science Reference 6703, 1970-1977; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Firestone Library 6702 Completed, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Firestone Library 6703 SSRC, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Firestone Library 6703 Post Office SSRC, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Firestone Library Reserve Reading Room 6704 - University Post Office, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Project 6704 Firestone Reserve Reading Room, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Firestone Library Reserve Reading Room 6704 - Consultants, Etc, 1963-1977; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 83-91 Prospect Street ALT 6800, 1968-1972; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stevenson Hall - Payments 6800, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Prospect 6802, 1968-1973; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Engineering and Mechanical Forms, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1960-1966; 1 box
    - Astrophysics Building, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Housing, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Married Graduate Student Housing, 1966-1964; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Pyne Administration Alterations, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Commons Modernization, 1965; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Frick Addition, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Frick Addition, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Water and Electricity Notes, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Department of Physical Planning Annual Reports to the President, 1965-1972; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Washington Road Safety Improvements, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Whig Hall, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Parking, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Planning - Master Plan, 1963-1967; 1 box
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Parking, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous and Data, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Planning for Co-Education, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Capital Planning, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Library, 1974-1982; 1 box
    - Correspondence #2, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript Library, 1975 October-1975 December; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Donor File, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Furnishings, 1976; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Mudd Library - Miscellaneous, 1982; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Green Hall, 1968-1969; 1 box
    - Green Hall, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Green Hall - Alterations I, 1969; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Green Hall - Alterations II, 1968; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Green Hall - Alterations III, 1968; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Prospect I - Plans, Correspondence, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Prospect II - Plans, 1969; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 185 Nassau Street Alteration, 1966-1972; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clio Hall - Personnel, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Frick, 1968; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Prospect Addition, 1969; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Prospect Center - Purchase Orders, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Third World Center - Contractor, Municipality, Miscellaneous, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Third World Center - Purchase Orders, Invoices, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Third World Center - University, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1938 Hall and 1939 Hall, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Third World Center - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gauss Hall, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Clio Hall, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dodge-Osborn, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Dormitories, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Nassau Hall - Miscellaneous, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Witherspoon - Purchase Orders, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Witherspoon - Purchase Orders, 1974; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Witherspoon, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dillon Gym, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - McCosh Hall 46, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Wyman House, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Field House - Minutes of Meetings, 1961 December 6-1963 April 23; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Engineering Quadrangle - Minutes of Meetings, 1959 September 18-1960 July 12; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Cage - Minutes of Meetings, 1964 April 2-1966 November 16; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Administration Building - Minutes of Meetings, 1964 April 28-1965 August 12; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lowrie House, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lowrie House, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New South, 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - West College, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dormitories, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Joseph Henry House, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - West College (7228), 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Prospect, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Jadwin, 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Jadwin, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dod Hall, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Alterations to Dod (7232), 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Eno Hall, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Guyot Hall - Mail Room, 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Edwards Hall (7235), 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - East Pyne, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Green Hall - Dr. Jacobs, 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Holder Hall Alterations, 1972; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Library, 1966-1977; 1 box
    - Agreements and Proposals, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Furnishings, 1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript Library, 1975 April-June; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript Library, 1966-1974; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript Library, 1975 January-March; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript Library, 1975 July-September; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Reports, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Purchase Orders, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Purchase Orders #1, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Purchase Orders #2, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dorm Kitchens, 1977; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Prospect, 1977; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Major Maintenance, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous - Financial Year, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Financial Year, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Elm Club, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Furniture, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Daily Manning Reports, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Engineering Quadrangle, 1971-1976; 1 box
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - University #3, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - University #1, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Consultants and Furniture, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1973; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Purchase Orders, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Consultants #1, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Consultants #2, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Contractors and Furniture, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - University #2, 1971-1976; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - New South, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Guyot Hall, 1968-1974; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Guyot Hall, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Art Museum (7156), 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - New South (7201), 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New South (7204), 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - McCosh Infirmary, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Grounds, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - New South, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 37 William Street, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - University Store, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 35 University Place (7210), 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 12-14 Dickinson, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Women's Toilet Alterations, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Nassau Hall Consultants, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Wilson College, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Guyot Hall, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Princeton Inn Game Room, 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Princeton Inn (7215), 1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Engineering Quadrangle Addition - Correspondence, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Engineering Quadrangle Addition - Purchase Orders, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Life Sciences - Budget, Miscellaneous, 1966-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commons, 1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Jadwin Physical Education Office, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Moffett Laboratory, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Madison Hall, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - McCosh Infirmary, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New South, 1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - McCarter Theater, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor Green Student Center, 1954-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Corwin Lounge, 1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Guyot Hall, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Woolworth Center, 1969-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Boat Storage, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - New Jersey Room - Firestone Library (7261-F), 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Firestone Library - New Jersey Room, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Holder Hall Toilet Alterations, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School - Hamilton Lounge, 1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Inscriptions, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Wilson/Edwards Alterations (7216/7217), 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Edwards Hall, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Patton Hall Purchase Orders, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Dormitories, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Henry Hall, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Patton, Henry and Lockhart Halls (7220), 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Nassau Hall (7221-2), 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Nassau Hall, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Major Maintenance - Financial Year, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Major Maintenance - Financial Year, 1979; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Museum Addition Proposal, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1879 Hall, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wilcox, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wyman House (Miscellaneous), 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Little (Miscellaneous), 1982; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Graduate College - Security Phones, 1981; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - P-3 Facility, circa 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Commons - Landscape Alterations to Madison Hall Entrance, circa 1975; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Carl Brauer, 1977; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Alterations to John C. Green Hall, 1977; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Additions and Alterations to the Woodrow Wilson School, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Laboratory (G.F.D.L.) Forrestal, Princeton University Computer Facility - Feasibility Study, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Adams, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Trustees, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Information for Bidders, circa 1966; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 185 Nassau Street - Acting Studio, circa 1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Yale, 1969; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Cornell, 1972; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Subcontractor - Equal Employment Opportunity, circa 1966; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lowrie House, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Elm Club, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - E-Quad, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Jones Hall, 1977; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Theobald Smith House, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Firestone (7818), 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Firestone (7818 #2), 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Firestone (7818 #3), 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - P. I. C. Furnishings, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 83 Springdale, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - West College - Admissions Study, 1978; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 33)